Puneet on strike, Bhavesh on non-strike.
That was a big shout from Dheeraj straight away.
Umpire Mr. Om Singh.
Standing
End Umpire Mr. Ravi Singh at Sq.
Just a single,
Puneet was looking for one more run but
Bhavesh said wait for a while, we don't want to take the risk.
So we got two semi-finalist teams after
Howden
Ping Panthers qualified
that will signal wide
outside the off line
so one is one team and admit Adens bowled
from the centre admit Adens won the toss
decided to bowl first they invited one is
one team to bat
we are the two destroyed batsmen on the
crease Punit and Bhavesh
two balls three runs no wicket
good strike straight to the fielder good
strike from Admit Titans also in the
fielding side
and now Bhavesh will face the first ball that
played with soft hands smartly at
square leg and single taken quickly
four balls five runs no wicket ball
in the air over the fielder there was a
chance here if he had gone a little back he would have
definitely taken the catch but it is a fraction of a
second chance you have to take it one time
and Dheeraj here
yes the frustration level there is always a smile on his face
247 five balls seven runs last ball of this over
Punit on strike
good ball ball in the block hole and
wanted to hit it directly but could
not hit it there  And one more run could have been added
and the over ended with one run, one was gone
for no loss and DJ wale babu play my
song.
Sagar to start the second over that's a
very good bowling look at the
line and length of the bowler and
looking for a big one able to connect Punit
and they will get one run
ninth no loss Bhavesh on strike
first to power play will they capitalise to get that
one and this time
backward region fine leg region that will run away
for four runs
yes waiting for the fun song
with bun 13 loss one I will one team
three four ball left in the power play
one fielder at standing at mid wicket deep
mid wicket
and one fielder at long on a
palti palti kya baat dashing brilliant four runs that's
the innovation from Bhavesh
not straight then
crooked quite an across
shot and four runs
Bhavesh got second boundary from bat 17 for
no loss and that's coming the unlucky number 17/1
bit off in the air
but safe out of danger one one team 18
for no loss
10 runs of the over so far
two balls to go
and after  Two balls that will be end of the
power play
looking to connect
time it well well will get a single inside
edge lucky
1.5 19 runs no wicket one one team
and this time angling down looking to play
that scoop shot
and no connection
end of over 19 runs after two overs
no wicket music music
so we had a fantastic two quarter finals it's a
quarter final number three
and we have one more quarter final coming
up after this match principal warriors
taking up with n they had a
great day first day in the league match
qualified for the quarter finals
19 runs after two overs no wicket
enough discussion here
about admi titans field setting that is a
fielding restriction will be
lifted maximum fielders can be
outside circle but minimum four fielders should be
inside circle
so the four fielders are short fine leg shot
third man one fielder at point and one at
shot extra cover
one fielder at deep square leg one fielder at
deep mid wicket
long off and long on
One fielder at deep cover. That's a field
setting from Adam Titans.
Would like to take two runs.  There may be danger but
not from Thros Direct.  I will take two runs here.
One shot.  So only single run.
One run shot.
So there was thunderous applause.  50% of it
is deducted.
20 for no loss.
This time he beat the fielder.  In the fine leg region.  The
ball is going out of the boundary for four runs.
Puneet and Bhosh have a big responsibility.
2.24 runs no wickets.
Both the batsmen are batting well.
Puneet and Bhosh.
Pushed lightly.  Two runs will be completed with this.   There may be
danger.  The throw is excellent and the
square leg umpire.  What will you say?  OUT.
There too, the one shot
song on demand Fasla Durant
is trending everywhere.  Even after the win, the
winning team has now become a stalwart except for BJ Bravo.
That's run out and Pune departs
2.3 24 for one
new batsman
Sunny Bhardwaj
coming in at number three
swings miss looking to play up and over
covers
no contact bat and ball beaten
2.4
at one one l one team initially won the toss
Admit Titans decided to field
and put One l one team in to bat
and this is out
excellent bowling performance here by Jaysh that's
a big wicket for one l one team 24
for two down
Admit Titans on the money Jaysh on the money
music
last ball of the third over 24 for two new
batsman Sudhanshu coming in
at number four.  Sudhanshu on
strike.
Just going down the leg side for a wide.
Umpire Mr. Om Singh signaling that
wide.
Both teams have made a great start
in this quarter final three.  Two wickets have been lost.
25 runs have been scored by One L One team
on this score board,
last ball of this over Jaysh has
pushed it lightly, just tap and play
and single taken,
so three gone, 26 for two, one all one team
and here one more run over throw but
there was backup fielder Rohit Nambalkar, he
stopped it,
so 30 for two 3.2 One and one teams,
a beautiful slide touch and single taken
31 for two
and looking to play that multiplicity shot,
the reverse hit
one run 3.5
33 for two,
Bhosh and Sudhanshu have a big responsibility, now
in the coming four overs we will have to do fireworks and some
explosive batting,
last ball the fourth over, make space, the
ball is going towards fine leg,
outside the boundary, for four runs, two
on 37 of four overs, one all one team,
four overs gone, 37 on the board, two wickets, the
lost,
if we play with the same momentum, then we would
like to cross the 80 mark here, One L One
team,
mean while music,
thank you DJ, will speed up a bit, all the
Cricketers have
little time here but we have less
time and need to cover many
matches.  So please speed up a bit all the
cricketers
four overs for 37 Sujeet Sujeet Yadav
change in bowling new bowler
this time blown down the track no
tried to play big strokes
but could not get the connection.
38 for two
Bhavesh is batting on 16 off eight with three fouls.
Pushed gently.  Shot to the
fielder at backward square leg, one run,
39 for two, Sudhanshu and Bhesh, there is a big
responsibility in the coming overs,
currently on nine runs, over the current run rate, they can
continue this momentum till the end,
this time he has played it over the fielder, is
this six runs, is this four runs for six runs,
powerful, brilliant,
from Sudhanshu's bat, Chak de phatte nab de
gilli, the ball was sent straight to Delhi, Delhi
made space and a lot of strength and
timing are very important here, it is not easy to play in this area.
45 for two with that big hit.
Multiple shot fielders are present there.  I'll
take one run here.  46 for two
no runs every over they maintain they no runs 10
runs to get at least 80 plus
46 for two
Bhavesh batting 17 of no
and Sudhanshu from 14 with one six
high in the chance and check gone very
well played by Bhavesh
46 for three down one and one team
that's a good catch again simple at Dheeraj
third man
last ball of the fifth over 46 for three
new batsman Prashant
and he missed it completely
after five overs 46 for three one all one team
music
five was gone 46 for three welcome back once again
good afternoon everyone those are watching
us live myself Mish Solanki welcoming you all we had
a fantastic day one and now day two
16 teams participated now all the teams
looking for that semi-final ticket
Dheeraj once again the skipper inu the bing attack
iss baar khela diya hai hawa mein
aur dekhna hoga one bounce chaar run
50 runs completed 50
Sudhanshu 18 off a win 146
53 One One team after 5.1
and that's high in the air oh he took that wow
that's MSD for you what a catch
excellent catch taken there what a catch
from the wicket wicket keeper
took about for Abhishek
absolutely great
cricket from the team Adammed Titans
fall of the fourth wicket here at 5.250 for
four One L One team
the new batsman coming at number six Sridhar
on strike.
Oh wow good bowling from Dheeraj.
Just a defense and quick singles taken.
51 for four.  A putting pressure on one l one
team they will restrict below 70 I think.
Admit IDence.
And that's a cracking shot.  Beats the fielder
at covers run away for four runs
or that was an excellent shot from Prashant
second ball boundary.
Yes he is a villain of one l one team
Prashant once
again looking to play for the big one they are
going for two they are going for two and they will get it
two runs
good running
and this over is turning out to be a good over for one one
team 11 runs so far in this over
one ball left 57 for four
looking for the big one they will go for two runs
and may be that will be a leg bye signal will be let
for the umpire signal umpire Ravi Singh
signalling leg bye after six overs
59 for four music
and we have the experience contain Rohit
Nimbalkar in the bowling attack six overs 59 for
four and
coming the last two overs of the first
innings 59 we talking about 7080
and let's see left arm round wicket
start with
and that's very good bowling keeping away
from the batsman's arc and that's a
good strategy from Rohit Nimbalkar
and this time high in the air
six runs
wow
excellent timing from Sridhar so
beautiful  So elegant just looking like a
wow
powerful super hit six six runs from
Sridhar
o got cut and bowled
this is the game of cricket pal me tola pal me masha thank
you DJ here one l one team
no one is doing any dance step so this song flopped
6.3 65 pe paanch Amit the new batter
iss baar seedha ke bat se khel diya hai.  We will
definitely go for two runs and two runs have been
taken here.  Good running between the wickets.
Amit is associated with Prashant.  One L One
team 67 for five.
Eight runs conceded, Rohit got one wicket.
And losing the momentum Rohit Nambalkar this
time strikes the ball a bit off the pitch line but
going down the leg side
great air four whom to win
chance
68 for five a bit of brazy air at Fatima
ground witnessing now o miss completely
full one from Rohit could
not connect here Amit
6.5 68 for five that's a last over coming up
off the penultimate over
last ball coming up off the penultimate over
and trying to bowl the fuller one but going
outside the off line one more extra
adding 69 for five we
talking about 70 they can get 80 also
69 for five last ball seventh over
one more wide
70 for five.
70 runs special for you 70 runs, 70 runs, 70 runs.
70 for five one and one team.
Last ball of the seventh over still to
complete as this time.  Good bowling.  Good
comeback from Rohit.
So from gone 745
so one one team makes some no
wow
music okay
seven overs 70 per five last over coming up of
the first innings of the quarter final
three
is on
Suraj Rathod what a strike excellent
shot just over fielder six for six
Runs 76 five
Prashant at his best once again
strike well and this fielder
takes it and gone there
is some question
and very well played makes some noise for
Prashant
good catch again by Harishal that is very good caught
at mid wicket
last four balls 76 for six wide
outside the off line
for wide
Ramesh the new batsman
oh clever bowling bowling at the middle of the
stumps
they looking for two runs and they will get it wow
good effort driving effort
two runs taken good running
last three balls we were talking about 80
here the score has reached close to 80.   They can get
85 plus
that will be the challenging total to chase for
admit titles.
Last three balls here we go
towards fine leg region only a single this
time.
It's 80 for six 80 on the board
80 per six
last two balls first innings quarter final
three of ICI Labord Proudly
Presents Brokers Premier League two to
six season three very well left
very flexible batsman just
like our brush is flexible the batsman
is also flexible like a brush
81 for six
last two balls 81 for six
that's a good strike at mid wicket region
and they will go for two runs and they will
reach the crease they will get
two runs
so last ball coming up 8 three for six
so one and one what do the team want we want we want we want let's
see will they hit a six or a four Amit
or will Admit Titans take the wicket.  Last ball of
the first innings.  83 for six.
A big hit would be 89 target 90.
One small hit for four.  87 Target Will Also
Be the Big One.  And this will be the big
game for both the teams.
Still one ball to go
is very flexible
Amit ko boss ne how flexible you are this is
a flexibility interview me question paasya tha
Amit ko how
flexible you are and this is example
in front of you 846
and this time not able to connect dot ball to
and
very good bowling
so make some noise for both the team excellent
performance admit titans one and one team
done pran warriors one the toss
related to ball first.  And let one team
to bat.
But before that a big target to chase for the
team
Adammed Titans not easy
on this pitch 85 we
have the two batters.
Walking on the field
and this is the biggest rivalry of the
tournament for one l one team admit
tides
we are Rohit Nibalkar and with
the other batsman
we are all in redness Rohit on strike
Saurabh on non strike and to start the
proceedings from one l one team
Prashant Inu the attack
left hand batsman
three, two one game on.
First ball in the air
and there was no attempt for the fielder to
just run ahead and take that catch.  Want to keep it
simple.
Not special.
Rohit off the mark with a single.  Now
Saurabh on strike.
That's a good strike but very good
fielding
towards Adam Wardish the mid off fielder
will get to run
good fielding by Amit
S a backup fielder Sunny was also helping
and that's teamwork for you
iss baar jhaj banayi uda diya hai.  The ball goes to
deep backward square leg
for four runs outside the boundary line.
That's what Adam made Titans capitalise on
in the power play to get maximum runs
scored.
And if you hit the ball off the pitch, the batsman
will punish you every time.
Seven runs no wicket
this time I am looking to play a cover
drive but he has got that outside edge and there is a
fielder at third man shot third man for a
single run
and that's a left right combination
burning the calories here of the fielders
and for the left hander there is a two
fielders one at square leg and one at wide long
on this
time completely beaten good bowling from
Prashant eight
runs conceded required run around 10
every over for the team admit Titans
again looking to swing good bowling from
Prashant back to back two dot balls
that went for wide.  Wait for that one more
ball to end of the first over.
That's a good strike fielder at long on
Amit they're
going for two runs but good throw
so one over gone 10 for no loss admit Titans
need 75 runs in seven overs music
but a second over Punit comes into the attack.
That's a two fielder setup at the on side
for the left hander.
One at mid-wicket and one at long on.  So mid
wicket is between that square leg and mid
wicket.   That's
a good strike.
I will go for two runs.
It's a very important match for both the teams
and especially Rohit Nimbalkar.
It is a big contender of leather ball cricket and he
has experience on this pitch many matches
being played and this time high in the air
chance for the catch but we land safe between the
two fielders and they are going for two runs
Saurabh is very quick Rohit is very quick
back to back two runs
and that is what they will look for 10 runs
every over they got already four runs in
first two balls
that are in the air o bit of misjudgement there may be that
sun reflection
two runs back to back two runs to two
six runs and they need just four runs in this
over to get that 10 runs but they will get
maximum runs as they
can score.
O good bowling good comeback from Punit
swinging in miss looking for a big connect
Rohit
1.46
wow good bowling into the block hole playing with
soft hands for a single
17 no wicket this is
waaaay good bowling from Punit first 10
runs from Prashant and now only seven runs in
five balls
last ball of the second over coming up
dancing down the track Amit O
that could be one more but he has saved that
boundary for sure and only single run
given
not easy to take that catch but good effort.
Big applause for Amit.
So, two have gone 18 for no loss and
need 67 runs in six overs.
One L One team has given a mountain-like target to
Admit Titans.  The target is 85.
And that's the end of the power play.
So the fielding restriction will be
lifted.  Maximum fielders can be
outside the circle but minimum four fielders
should be inside the circle
and that's it. Let's see who will bowl the next
over from one of the teams. That's Amit coming
into the attack.
That's a full fielder setup. Shot third man, shot
fine leg, shot
cover
and shot mid wicket. We will be
interested to watch this over
from Amit because of the left-right combination
setting up the field.
Shot fine leg is much wide,
and shot third man is square, shot cover and
shot mid wicket. That's what
the captain knows and for the left-
hander, we will be interesting to watch. The field
settings are
long on
deep square leg, deep mid wicket.
And here we go Amit to Rohit. The
battle between Amit and Rohit
is clever in the air.
Direct hit could be the chance. Very
close call.
One run taken.
19 for no loss.
Tried to hit an ultimatum shot but could
not connect.
Saurabh bowls a
full toss ball.  Just tapping it away for a single
straight to the field at covers.
Good stop by Sunny.
Only three runs given away in four balls.
Amit
and Rohit will want a big hit in this over.   You will bring
an incarnation of yourself.  Adam
Gilchrist, Suresh Raina, Matthew Hayden,
Chris Gayle,
Yuvraj Singh, Abhishek Sharma, great,
legendary batsmen.   The
most dangerous were the Lance Closers from South
Africa.
Good ball this time
no runs here
rent for dot ball last ball coming off only
three runs conceded in this over
and that's gone for a big one banking on the
ro six run
shot off pitch lane the batsman will punish you
every time
three overs 27 runs no wicket that was
massive hit one of the longest
six of the tournament
lose with that single at long off once again
Saurabh one strike
that's a very good stop from Sunny and
follow through.
So only two runs conceded in four balls in
this over.
High in the air
Puneet drops it.
That could be taken could be
the big wicket
but batsman Sourav survives
30 for no loss with that single and last
ball coming up of the fourth over
and this time connected well high in the air
on the way all the way
Rohit ne kar diya hai match ko superhit
23 two big hits in 14 balls
thank you DJ four overs 36 no wicket
and 49 runs needed in four overs one oil one team
or Admet Titans so I
would like to check here who will win brother will win no
one will win only we will win.
[laughter] The
cricket game will win.  One L One Team.  If
you are supporting one l one team makes some
noise.
If you're supporting Adami Titans makes some
noise.   He has
come from a very far distance.  There is noise here from Kanyakumari.
And now coming four overs as almost 50
runs needed in four overs 49 from 24
new big attack from one one team Sudhanshu.
And that's high in the air
and the umpire is checking for six runs wow would you
believe it six runs
excellent timing very well played that was a
big one from Saurabh
Rohit has already got to hit big and
now Saurabh is joining the party in the fire
works for a maximum hit for six.  Wow
18 of 11 with 1416 and Rohit 23 of 14 with
two big hits.
This partnership is burning the cataclysms.
42 runs scored and 43 runs needed.  It has reduced by half.
Half is left.
Very interesting match
over this time a clever bowling good comeback
from Sudhanshu.   They have a
couple of overs to get more pressured
by Adam Titans
and one l one team will try the level best
and good bowling change in the bowling variation has
made the trick completely beaten
and that's a good strike high and into the
sky six r kiya hai
Saurabh and Rohit ne so 37 runs needed
in 20 balls that was a
big shot big appeal may be
hitting on body
one for dot ball 48
12 runs of the over bit expensive from
Sudhanshu
37 runs in 19 balls
o good bowling good come back good come back from
Sudhanshu
on the fourth ball he has been hit for six
but very good comeback back to back two dot
balls a beauty of delivery two and five o's
gone 48 for no loss and 37 runs needed in three overs
music
this will be very two interesting
teams contest playing for the semi final
ticket
Rohit and Saurabh the experts
work today
37 runs in 18 balls  Not easy yet one l one
team will have to make a comeback here, will
try to take the wicket here, the
ball has been blown in the air and will try to take the wicket
but hey what happened, how did this happen, it seemed as if the
catch was taken, ups was
dropped and it could have been the game changing
moment, that could have been the game changing moment, had the catch been taken the tables could have
turned.
Rohit is lucky as he
completes 50 runs.
Just a single from Adils.
No wickets yet for both the batsmen on fire, Saurabh
and Rohit.
34 runs in 16 balls is still difficult.
Both teams are trying.   They need at least
10 balls they will
defend one by one team they
change in the field settings
full toss ball and excellent stop from the bowler will get
a single by Punit
33 runs in 15 balls still the chase is on that's a
very good bowling from Prashant.
That's clever.
This ball was kept far away from the batsman.   He did
not let it come on his bat and here is the
bowling performance by Prashant.
And something in mission and taken would you believe it what a
catch but take of Rohit Nimbalkar
very well played
team can the match turn here
so one and one team supporters is there a
twist in the tale that
first wicket fall a big relief
for the one l one team
5.5 52 for one and 33 runs in 13 balls one over has to be
defended in the coming over we have to
see who
that bowler will defend
interesting match
and Prashant has got the breakthrough at very right
point of time.  Good catch again
by Sridhar at backward region.
Here goes Harshal the new batter.  Shot Pitch Ball
And That's Gone High In The Air Will Land Safe.   They are
going for two runs, chance for the run
out their direct hit.  But the keeper has done the
job one more wicket fall
and here the one l one team is trying the
effort is continuing
excellent batting from Prashant
that's the end of the over number six
53 for two and need 32 runs in two overs
32 runs and 12 balls.
So the One & One team is trying its best.
He says that a boat does not cross the ocean by being afraid of the waves.  A
boat cannot cross the ocean by being afraid of the waves
and those who try are blessed.
What is the matter.  You have completed it.
32 runs in 12 balls.  Music
so let's check who will win Admet Titans or
One L One Team so brother will win
brother will win
Admet Titan supporters make some noise
wow what a thing on One One Team supporters
make some noise it's a
draw between the two
32 to 12
and a very serious discussion has ended.
That's a quick DRM ended
32 runs in 12 balls 16 runs every over 16
runs per over we have to
see how the One L One team will
try its best to defend this match in this over now here we go
32 runs in 12 balls
Tejas the new batter good strike
very good throw quick reflexes
Sudhanshu once again in the bowling attack
31 runs in 11 balls
Tejas the new bat on strike
o excellent bowling
and what a strategy here that's
a suicidal run out but it doesn't matter
thanks DJ needs 31 runs in 10 balls
Sourav on strike only man can change the
course of the match
o no o no full toss ball and it will go
no ball and six runs.
That's the seven-run gift from one L1 team
to Adamat Titans.
What has happened?  How did it happen?  Why did it happen?   Is
this a match changing ball moment for Adam
Titans.
24 runs needed in 10 balls and a free hit
ball.
And that's a good strike high wow six
runs
excellent shot stunned
Saurabh at his best
extra and now six runs and this is
turning on to a good over 14 runs in three
balls so far 18 runs needed in nine balls and
here the on field discussion is full to cost
what a match roller coast quarter final
three
witnessing on Fatima Grounds
on the iconic cricket ground in Mumbai
and Saurabh fourth six from his bit of 21
four and four maximums hit in nine balls for 18
runs
oh excellent bowling
still pressure on here Adammed
Titans Sudhanshu will be
looking for a wicket off Saurabh
18 runs needed in eight balls
this time good bowling good strike will they go
for two runs for sure
direct throw but two runs taken
16 runs in seven balls
either
one wicket and one six
what a match
wow wow and wow six runs
four and five sixes.
10 runs needed in one over.
22 Rans Came In That Over.
Seven overs, 75 for three.
Good batting from Saurabh.
Thank you DJ.  So if you are a fan of Saurabh
and Admit Titans.
Friends, let's give a big round of applause to Saurabh.  Very well
plaid.  46 off 23 1 and 56 is not easy to
play on this Fatima ground.
Good batting.
And tension rising heart dhak dhak dhak dhak dhak dhak dhakdhak
10 runs needed in six balls and Amit is
will bowl at it looks like yes Amit going to
bowl
Sagar will take strike 10 runs six balls
quarter final three who will
enter the semi final will
defend
or chase here will have to be seen interesting to watch
what a match will make
some changes in fielding point has
now been sent towards deep point there is
a fielder shot third man shot fine leg shot
shot cover and shot mid wicket inside the
circle.
Very Important Field Setup.
And we are all in readiness.
10 runs six balls here we go.
Excellent fielding only a single run
nine runs five balls and the destructive
stalwart batsman Saurabh on strike
if this wicket is taken
this big fish needs to be netted
no runs five balls
wow good bowling good bowling from Amit
went for a dot ball tension rising
on Admet titans nine runs needed in four balls wow
what a match
oh no oh no that's a
fuller one ends
above the height waist height
and square leg umpire signals no ball that's
no ball given and coming up the free hit
eight runs needed in four balls.
Yes clever bowling in the block hole.  Will they
go for two only for a single run?  That's a good
throw at this striker and this is the
wicket.
The much needed break through for the One One team.   There was a
little mix up
and the wicket fell.
Sagar will go here and seven runs are needed
in three balls.
Good throw from Prasanth.  Excellent throw
from Prashant.
Three balls and seven runs.  Dheeraj captain
on strike.  It's a big responsibility
and this time I've played it.  The ball is going
outside the boundary line,
explosive
stalwart Dheeraj Sonavani
what a match, what a match
three runs needed in two balls there is still a chance one and one
team both balls both wickets have to be taken
oh ho ho
bit of mind games over there trying for
one cutting wicket
three three runs two balls
oh good bowling
believe wow good bowling and that could be the out
run out suicidal run out
and yes a big serious discussion that is changing the
strike
what will be the last ball and who will take
the strike is a big question
one ball three runs
what a match
fasten your seat belts the weather has become
exciting.  Don't go anywhere,
friends.  The heartbeat has become faster.
Breathing has stopped.  The weather has changed.  The atmosphere has become
heated.
Who will make whom miserable?  Who will become
rich?   Keep
watching.  Cod Final Three in progress.
One ball left.  Still unable to say who will win
this match.  One ball three runs what does the
bowler's mind say what does the batsman's mind say
what does the mind of our audience my mind my mind
my mind this is only you will witness this
excitement in ICICI Lomb proudly
presenting Brokers Premier League 226
Season Three Sunday Funday who will fly whose
punishment one
ball three runs here we go oh that's a very
good stop.  This could be a
chance for the run out.  This could be the chance for a
run out.
o
Match scores are level.
What a match, what a contest
and we are expecting a super over.
Both the teams have performed brilliantly.
What a match, what a contest.
What a battle
but take off Amit the driving
effort he made and the stop he made in the follow through
because of that he could
not take the second run three runs
and it will be interesting the watch
and the super over mean while music DJ
thank you DJ thank you very much onak onak
both of you
everyone is welcome and once again ICICI Lob
presents
Brokers Premier League 2 season three
quarter final three
and the team Prudent Warriors is eagerly waiting for
our turn when will we do
fireworks
they must have eaten twice already
Prudent Warriors
but let's move towards the super over and we go all in
readiness once again
Saurabh and Rohit here we
go first ball on the super over
looking for a big got the outside edge
only a single run
Prashant
started bowling that
six balls and only two wickets
excellent bowling totally beaten.  Rohit
wanted to connect.
Good bowling now by Prashant
two balls only one run
excellent bowling into the block hole only a
single run good start from one all one
team
three balls only two runs
three balls two runs
very good bowling clever bowling not allowing
the batter to hit only a single
four balls only three runs
what a start to this super over contest
two balls to go and Rohit will look for some
big fire wickets
and that's
out
and the question from Rohit Nimbalkar the
aggression like Ricky Bunting
only three runs and five balls.   I do
n't know what magic Prashant has done.
Daya, find out what is the secret behind this.
Commentator Kassar
last ball to go super over
two runs le jayenge definitely
and only two runs
five runs and only six to win music
Adam Titans
or one l one team six runs
three to one game on
six to get six runs to win one l one team
and that's a good strike.
That will go all the way for four runs.
Just two runs away now.
What a strike.
Awesome loud bang bang
And one all one team is ready to dance on the
floor one two one two three four get on the dance
floor music
And yes only one is needed
so one all one team are you ready?
One two three four dance floor
needs a run.
And that's the victory.
one the super over and